# Shariar Ahmed

example.com (347)-222-5449

Shariar001Ahmed@gmail.com

Linkedlı

http://linkedin.com/in/shariar-ahmed

GitHub

https://github.com/SaintShariar

### **PROJECTS**

### **Budget Tracking Web Application**

In this web dev project, I utilized HTML and CSS to craft an engaging user interface and design. Employing HTML for structuring content and CSS for styling, I created a well-organized portfolio with multiple tabs and clicks, enhancing user experience. The thoughtful use of these technologies ensures a visually appealing and seamlessly navigable showcase of my web development skills and projects

### **Web Portfolio**

In this web dev project, I utilized HTML and CSS to craft an engaging user interface and design. Employing HTML for structuring content and CSS for styling, I created a well-organized portfolio with multiple tabs and clicks, enhancing user experience. The thoughtful use of these technologies ensures a visually appealing and seamlessly navigable showcase of my web development skills and projects.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### ATLANTA POLICE DEPARTMENT | 2022 - 2023

December 2022 - June 2023

## NYC DEPARTMENT OF CITYWIDE ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICE | 2020 - 2022

June 2023 - December 2022

#### **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor of Science | Electrical Engineering

University at Buffalo JAN' 18 - MAY' 21

### Bachelor of Science | Electrical Engineering

Buffalo State College

### **Skills**

### **Programming**

Javascript | Python | CSS |
HTML | SQL | Git | React |
Java | C# | Node.Js | Vue
Native | Jira | PHP | Linux |
Go | Ruby | MongoDB |
Angular | JQuery | Angular |
Bootstrap | AWS | Apache |
Nginx | C++ | Azure |
Docker | .NET | C++ | C |
Express | Typescript |
CI/CD | Cloud Computing |
Front-end | Back-end | Full
Stock | Redux |